Is she poking fun at me?
Even people without friends use line, you know?
So what if it's only to text my family?
Yeah, I partake a bit.
It's not a drink.
Look, these stickers are so hilarious.
Should have guessed they'd be boring.
If you want, I'm happy to send them to you.
No, thanks.
You know, our class doesn't have a group chat to discuss projects and things, huh?
But I think class two has one.
They're always trying to play themselves off as a team.
Uh, the basketball club had one too.
Speaking of which, does your club have one?
Why are we even talking about this?
I don't think they do.
But maybe I just wasn't invited to join it.
Then we should ask.
What?
No thanks.
Why though?
Huh?
It's such a small club.
If they haven't invited me, it's because they don't want me in it.
Don't she even knows what it's like to get left out.
Must be weird for her.
Can I leave it that ball?
Oh, I should love it.
What time does it know?
That's that class.
I don't think it was Jon Mutta.
See you next week.
I'll travel back to scenes in the fort.
influenTS there.
мин.
You look at the movies, runes with winners.
Maybe the night you sleep during this week or not.
Maybe you're the clothing part of or not.
I know your Drew Loyalagaar근 from things.
Okay, so Whoa.
What do that now?
What do that?
What the stuff does?
What do you mean?
What do you have to know when children tend to sing?
I know your kids who are dancing.
Transcription by ESO. Translation by —
It's boned Head like this
赤根射す日は柔らかに弾けた シャヨーニ 僕らは目も開かぬまま
悲しくってしようがないんだ お日様で手が濡れた
眩しくって仕方がないし 途方に暮れた帰り 落ちてゆくように
茜が射したからもう少して 僕は僕を一つは愛せたのに
シャヨーニ 気づけば目も開かぬまま
雫な夕落の中 僕らは目も開かぬまま
I have to get a boyfriend before Christmas.
Sure.
Come on, you can at least give me a Me Too.
Wanting about wanting one will never actually get me one, though.
I need to make some actual moves.
What sort of moves?
Hmm, like, I know, exchanging line ideas with all the boys in class.
Right, good luck with all that.
Good idea!
Well, finally on board, are you?
Finding a boyfriend would be as easy as breathing for Yamada.
Go out with me!
As you wish!
Ugh, leave Yamada out of this!
Hi there.
Wha?
Huh?
Whoa now, hang on!
Why send a level 99 out to handle slimes?
Slimes?
Well, I thought we were supposed to exchange IDs with everyone in the class.
Oh yeah, that's right.
Okay, Ichi, give me your line.
Ichi?
Can I just give you my code?
Here.
Wait, but...
Okay, there you are.
Hey, your profile pic is Rem.
Wait, you know her?
Yeah.
My brother's a real bona fide otaku.
Though I'm more of a Rom fan myself.
Living proof some gyaru types are nice to nerds.
Huh?
What happened?
What's with that bloodlust?
Okay.
At your level, you really need to handle the higher ups, Anna.
Huh?
Hmm.
Like in this class, we've got Ishimuro.
Ishimuro may be an average looking guy, but he's an ace on the track team and one of the brightest in class.
Go ask the cutie!
You're the one who really wants his ID, Moe.
You know what?
He lives in my building.
What?
Are you close then?
Uh...
Well...
Uh-huh.
Our parents get along.
We talk when we see each other.
The same apartments?
Co-apartments?
So...
They basically live under the same roof is what she's saying!
Do you already know his line ID?
No, actually.
Go get asking, then!
Even like my mom said-
No!
Don't!
I won't be close!
Oh my god!
Oh...
Uh...
Hey...
Um...
Uh...
I have no real reason to stop her, though...
Ishimuro, do you use line?
Uh...
Wait...!
Shhh...
Ichikawa, do you use line?
Yeah, I...
Why?
Uh...
Let's exchange IDs!
Is she trying to...
Ah!
Huh?
No, I, um, just, uh, yeah.
Knew that kid was a weirdo.
What's with him?
Sorry, never mind.
No, chill out.
There's no way.
But what if...
I, I just better make sure to tell her next time.
I do use it.
I do.
Do you ever check if your sis is up to date?
Yes, I do!
Wait.
Whoa, you tried to date your sister?
What a perv!
Okay, now pull your mouth wide and say,
I need to pack.
Yamada was trying to exchange line IDs with me.
But she's got tons of friends.
She doesn't need to add me.
Exchanging IDs is probably no big deal for her.
Yamada likes guys who are...
distant and current.
But really nice under the surface.
Kind of charming, a little awkward.
Guys like that don't exist in real life!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, settle down.
You always hanging around like that because you like me?
What's this gloomy guy doing talking like that?
What if he's wrong?
He's not, though.
That's opportunism for you.
Stop.
No!
This train of thought is bad!
Quit giving yourself hope!
Stop!
Only ended up getting through three pages yesterday.
It's really a lot of fun, you know.
The new Dead or Dead game.
So then, want to come over and try it?
At least try to hide your ulterior motives.
Yamada here only plays cutesy games like Animal Cross Seas.
What's that?
You don't know?
Good work, Kobayashi.
Keep up that iron defense.
This again?
But that girl, who is she?
Think that's his girlfriend?
If it was, he wouldn't have the balls to be blatantly going after Yamada like this, right?
Of course he would.
Guy's a real known polygamist around here.
For not liking him, you sure know a lot about the Kree.
You can come too, then, Kobayashi.
Huh?
Seriously.
I wanted you to, right from the start.
I think it'll be fun playing with two girls.
Seriously?
Like anyone believes that for a second.
He clearly only cares about Yamada.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I mean, yeah, I, uh, that's cool.
I could totally go.
Chi?
What a pushover!
Well, there we have it, then.
Feel free to come with Yamada.
Two girls will be twice the fun.
This is bad.
This is really bad.
Her steel fortress just came crumbling down.
So what's with the silent treatment?
I'm not going over to that guy's place.
Fine.
I'll just invite Moe, then.
You're really going?
I mean, don't see why I wouldn't go.
It's not going to be fun.
That's not very nice, is it?
Why would you say something like that?
Yamada's too nice to break it to her.
She doesn't want to say she's only bait.
I mean, that guy, well, he's, you know, he's just...
She's no good at being mean.
Are you really trying to badmouth him right now?
That's not something you do, Yamada.
What?
Just forget it.
But I warned you.
What's your deal?
What?
I really need to find a way to stomp out Senior Pickup Artist.
What's the matter?
Uh, uh, it's nothing.
Just thought I might read outside for a change.
She caught me worrying about her.
How pathetic.
Do you ever play video games, Ichikawa?
Mm-hmm.
Just on Smitch, I guess.
And I only got that a little ways back.
Tatsuo got a Smitch from his parents, you know?
Already?
Awesome.
I mean, I played the demo at Yodo, but the controls were kind of dumb.
That thing's for casual gamers.
The memories I sealed away are coming back to me!
Uh, are you okay?
Yeah, it's nothing.
Don't worry.
My dad plays video games, so we have everything at home.
Smitch, play Saturn, and some PC thing.
He really likes it all, actually.
So then I said...
Oh, Yamada's in here as well.
Huh?
That's the girl!
Oh my, you were right!
She's so cute!
Sorry about earlier.
It's just Haria...
I mean, Nanjo can get a little carried away sometimes.
An obvious foe slip-up.
Trying to drive home how buddy-buddy they are.
Honestly, with those looks, I'm sure you already have a boyfriend anyway.
Huh?
I don't have a boyfriend.
Yeah, sure.
Seriously, I really don't.
Oh, wait, I get it.
She's on TV and stuff, so she's gotta pretend.
Can't have her reputation ruined.
I really don't have one!
I don't, you know.
Oh.
Sure.
Huh?
What?
Wait, what was she so surprised about?
Did I do something?
Wait, but what?
Hey, um...
Yeah?
You...
You shouldn't hang out with me when people are around.
What's this about?
Just come on!
Senior pickup artist?
Shoot!
Huh?
Wha...
What?
Oh...
Huh?
察riya!
Wait!
Uh...
Uh Mmm...
Sorry, I felt...
Oops!
Uh, um, sorry, I didn't mean, let's get going.
Okay, so what was that about?
We were supposed to move apart.
Getting that close is going to give people the wrong idea.
Are you kidding me?
Don't you get it yet?
But Yashiko, he's just trying to get Anna to come over.
You're being used as bait.
Huh?
Haven't you figured out that guy's a real creepoid?
No, you idiot, that's what's great about him.
I, I, I...
What? Kobayashi?
I, I know! Of course I know!
Duh! I'm not a dumbass or anything.
This, this is hard to watch.
See, I knew, and I said yes anyway.
That's how much it doesn't matter to me, okay?
I'm completely fine!
Um, hey, hey, Yamada?
Yoo-hoo, you listening?
Yamada? Miss Yamada?
Anna? Annie?
Dumb she-giant!
Huh?
Get back here!
Wait!
How'd you get so fast?
Ow! Stop it! Cut it out!
What's up?
Oh, nothing.
Just...
I decided not to go
to Creep's house.
Oh, you!
What am I going to do with you?
Oh, brother, here we go.
And so, peace returns to the girls.
That guy doesn't really think
that we're actually
like
me and Yamada are...
No, of course he doesn't.
The only reason me and Yamada
were together was...
But Yashiko,
he's just trying to get
Anna to come over!
You're being used as bait!
So then,
was she
using me?
Of course she was.
She used me to shake off
a guy who wouldn't
take a hint.
Me.
A guy she doesn't even like.
Maybe she always...
has been.
That explains it all.
Good morning.
Hey!
Morning.
I haven't been back
to the library since.
Not yesterday.
Not the day before, either.
I don't even care anymore.
I don't even care.
Are you mad at me?
How come?
I was thinking about going tomorrow.
Come on!
Because I'm always so close to you.
Oh.
She's worried about what I said before?
That's not it.
Whatever.
I've got places to be.
I'm sorry.
Does she take a hit to her pride?
Upset that the guy she thought she was using hates her now?
Right.
It's so obvious.
Of course.
I knew from the start, didn't I?
No.
That's not the kind of girl Yamada is.
I just wanted an excuse.
To hate her.
Do you want me to tell mom you want it?
No.
It wasn't even that good.
You played for two whole hours.
I wanted it more than anything, but knew it was hard to come by.
I was afraid of getting too obsessed.
Sorry.
I had stuff to do during lunch break.
That's all it was.
Really?
So you're not mad?
No.
I'm...
Sorry.
That was a makeup hug.
You don't like being close though, do you?
I never said that.
Okay?
You always hanging around like that because you like me?
Shut up.
Away with you!
Let's go home together.
Yeah.
Oh, and Ichikawa, do you know the best way to eat natto?
If you stir it around 40 times, it's really good.
Sorry.
The truth is, I'm not big on natto, actually.
Peso sooner then.
I just went on and on about it.
Yeah, that's why it's kinda hard to say anything to you.
Me and Yamada really have different senses and tastes.
This is where we split.
Wait!
What?
Hold on a second.
Let's talk some more.
How bad is she hurting to talk about natto?
I sometimes don't mind natto and fried rice.
What now?
What is it?
Are you going anywhere over winter break?
What's with the change of subject?
Y-yeah, I am.
We're all going to visit my dad's hometown.
Oh, yeah?
Where's that?
Akita.
Oh!
They've got good food there.
I think it's called...
It's a...
Ki...
Tan...
Hong Kong?
Kiri Tangpon.
You weren't even close!
Oh, and that namahage comes around every night too, doesn't it?
Not every night.
That would be an awful place.
Oh!
I meant to give this back to you.
Had it in my bag a while.
Huh?
What did you think?
Better than I expected.
Which part did you like best?
I liked this really cute part at the beginning.
Yeah, when they both make notes in the margins of their notebook.
Uh...
Yeah!
Me too!
Yeah.
I'll bring the next one on Monday.
Huh?
Nothing.
I'll bring the next one on Monday.
Huh?
Hmm...
Not....
Huh?
I'll bring the next one on Monday.
Nothing.
Yeah, me too!
Yeah?
I'll bring the next one on Monday.
Huh?
Nothing. I'll bring the next one on Monday.
Okay, see ya!
See ya.
Hey, wait up a second!
Busted.
No boyfriend again!
Oh well.
Sorry! I forgot to bring the next volume with me to school.
That's fine. Don't worry about it.
But I'll bring it tomorrow.
You can't. Winter break starts tomorrow.
Oh, yeah. Well then, guess we'll have to end up meeting each other somewhere.
You really don't have to go through all that trouble.
No, no, I do! Volume 3 ends on a real cliffhanger, right? I mean, you have to read the rest of it!
That's some pressure.
Hey, Yamada!
You go on ahead!
Oh...
So...
Give me your line ID.
Okay...
So tomorrow then!
Kyu...
Okay...
Tomorrow...
Tomorrow?
I know.
Good night.